[silence]
Hey! Hey!
We don't need your nagging cover
We're too poor, shy of superstardom
No glossy photos, no billboard chart
Sleeping on couches, playing basements
Free minds won't bow to a corporate arch
They want us clean-shaven, posing pretty
Selling our souls for a ten-year plan
But we'd better stink of cheap PBR
Then sell our songs to a greased-up man
Why isn't our souls for a flashy tour?
No, we'll leave that ship at the dock
Your velvet ropes and VIP rooms get f*cked right off
Still not famous, still not sorry
Rather bleed truth and borrow their story
Yo, A&R telling us what to play
We write our own rules and sing our own way
Still not famous, still not sorry
Rap too proud for sorry-story
Keep it in a gorge, crank it 'til it bleeds
Freedom's our drug, face just a disease
They promise exposure, a million streams
But it's just state of mind in your teenage dreams
We're fine with free fans in a sweaty room
Trading our fame for creative perfume
No neon signs, no corporate bailout
We live for the core changes in our veins
If the scene goes sideways, we'll still stay true
'Cause selling us the only thing that's lame
Call track for gold bars and grand illusions
We laugh so hard we almost pissed
We're allergic to mansions and red-guitar solos
Give us scrappy real, not famous, still not sorry
Rather bleed truth and borrow their story
No, A&R telling us what to play
We write our own rules and sing our own way
Still not famous, still not sorry
Rap too proud for sorry-story
Keep it in a gorge, crank it 'til it bleeds
Freedom's our drug, face just a disease
No leather jackets in boardrooms
No punched up smiles for apt campaign pains
We'll stay broken, loud and restless
While your stars decay in fame's chains
Still not famous, still not sorry
We'd rather bleed truth than bother sorry
No, A&R telling us what to play
We write our own rules and sing our own way
Still not famous, still not sorry
Rap too proud for sorry-story
Keep it in a gorge, crank it 'til it bleeds
Freedom's our drug, face just a disease
[ Silence ]